entertainment.ie 2019-06-24

# Entertainment.ie : Cinema, TV, Listings, Celebrity Gossip, Photos, Clubbing, Theatre, Reviews, Trailers, Lotto

* * *

This website, entertainment.ie and associated apps is owned and operated by Packed House Ltd. 

In this Privacy Policy, when we refer to "entertainment.ie", we mean the digital network operated by entertainment.ie, or its parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates. 

Entertainment.ie is fully compliant with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679, which is in effect from May 25th 2018. 

* * *

**Advertising Consent Revocation**

entertainment.ie respects your right to choose. Consent revocation is the process by which EEA (European Economic Area) visitors who consented to personalized ads can revoke that consent. 

Click here to revoke your choice

* * *

**Website Notification Consent Revocation**

entertainment.ie uses Xtremepush to send in-browser messages. All of this information collected is of a non-personally identifiable nature. Users may opt in by choosing to do so upon a browser prompt. Users may opt out via their browser settings or you can click here to change your choice. 

Click here to change your choice

* * *

**Right to Privacy**

entertainment.ie respects your right to privacy. Any information we collect, be it non-personalised or personalised, will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with The General Data Protection Regulation. Entertainment.ie strictly only works with fully data compliant partners. 

* * *

**Collection and use of personal information**

entertainment.ie collects non-personalised and personalised data in three main ways: 

Information that you actively volunteer, such as account registration, email newsletter registration and similar. 

Analytics: This allows entertainment.ie to measure the number of visits to the website, content consumed and helps inform us as to how to improve the website for visitors. 

Advertising: Advertisers on entertainment.ie use cookies to inform, optimise and serve ads based on your browsing activities and interests. 

We never share this information with any third parties without your explicit consent. 

For more information on how to manage your cookies please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://entertainment.ie/content/cookies/). 

**The information we collect:**

**Advertising**

Advertisements on entertainment.ie can be of a non-personalised or personalised nature. The information collected by advertisers helps them to gauge the effectiveness of their campaigns and may limit the number of times you see an advertisement. For more information and details of how to manage how advertising works on entertainment.ie, read our [Cookies Policy](https://entertainment.ie/content/cookies/). 

**Change of Advertisement Consent**

entertainment.ie respects your right to choose. Under the GDPR you may change your choice of viewing personalised and non-personalised advertisements. You may do so by changing your consent options. 

**Entertainment.ie Reader Accounts**

You may register for a free entertainment.ie reader account. Your account allows you to enter competitions on our website, customise your cinema and tv listings as well as receive notification reminders. 

The information we collect and store securely includes name, email address, location, date of birth, competition entry details, reminders, log in and updating account details. We need this information to send your reminders, check the validity of competition entries, and for storing your favourite tv stations and cinemas on our systems. 

You may change your account settings or opt out at any time by [deleting your account](https://entertainment.ie/my-account/sign-in/). 

**Entertainment.ie Partner Listing Accounts**

You may register for a free entertainment.ie listing partner account to submit event listings. The information we collect and store securely includes name, email address, phone number, the venue or act you represent, the events you have submitted, log in and updating account details. 

We need this information to verify the events that are submitted are valid and do not contravene our terms of use. 

You may opt out of our partner listing account at any time by [deleting your account.](https://entertainment.ie/my-account/sign-in/)

**Email Newsletters**

You may register for informational email newsletters via our website. This requires your name and email address, and optionally your county and areas of interest, to be submitted to our email newsletter software (XtremePush), which is fully compliant with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). [Read XtremePush's Privacy Policy.](https://xtremepush.com/privacy-policy/)

You may choose to opt out of email newsletters or update your preferences at any time via the unsubscribe link in the foot of any of our email newsletters or from the signup form on our website . You may also choose to opt out by contacting [info@entertainment.ie](mailto:info@entertainment.ie) at any time. 

**Email Contact by You**

If you email entertainment.ie with feedback or questions, we will respond to you as quickly as possible. Any details you send to us, including email and name, are stored for as long as is necessary to deal with your query. All contacts are deleted once we have satisfactorily answered your question or comment. 

**Competition Winners List**

We like to provide all readers with the names of winners of competitions. We will always request permission from the winner to display their name on the list and only display this for 3 months. Any winner has the right not to have their name published. There may be some instances of us not being able to display full names on our winners list for security or operational reasons. 

* * *

**Third Party Applications**

We use some third party services on our website. We only use GDPR compliant services and partners. 

**Analytics Services**

These services help us build a better website experience. We use [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy), [Hotjar](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy), [Firebase](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/) and [Permutive](https://permutive.com/privacy/) for this purpose. Hotjar and Firebase anonymise your IP and do not contain any personally identifiable information. Google Analytics does capture some personal information, such as location information. Permutive only collects non personalised data to analyse what content is consumed to help provide more relevant content groups for our readers. Read their Privacy Policies & options on how to opt out by clicking on the links above. These companies do not share your data with any other companies. This information will never be disclosed to a third party, unless obliged to do so by a rule of law.

**Advertising**

We schedule our advertising on site and in app with Google’s Ad Manager. Any information collected and stored can be personalised or non-personalised; you have the option to choose your preference when visiting our website for the first time and you can change your preferences in our Privacy Policy. Some cookies are used for non personalised ads. [Read our Cookies Policy](https://entertainment.ie/content/cookies/). 

**Messaging Service**

From time to time we may provide users with useful directions on how to best to experience our website (tool tips), or highlight particular messages to our users. We use [Xtremepush](https://xtremepush.com/privacy-policy/) to deliver such on site & in app messaging. Read their [Privacy Policy](https://xtremepush.com/privacy-policy/). Users may opt out via their browser settings or you can click here to revoke your choice. 

**Competitions & Surveys:**

**Wufoo**

Entertainment.ie occasionally uses Wufoo for competition entry collection. We will clearly inform you when we are using this service. Wufoo is owned and operated by Survey Monkey. [Read Wufoo’s Privacy Policy.](https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/legal/privacy-policy/). 

**Survey Monkey**

Entertainment.ie occasionally uses Survey Monkey to run reader surveys. We will clearly inform you when we are using this service. [Read Survey Monkey’s Privacy Policy.](https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/legal/privacy-policy/). 

**Social Media & Website Players**

Entertainment.ie offers readers the opportunity to share and view our content on various social media platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Google+, Instagram & Flickr. Entertainment.ie also uses GDPR compliant third party audio and video players as well as quiz generating tools. These include Youtube, Soundcloud, Omny and Playbuzz and PollDaddy. 

You can read each of their Privacy Policies by visiting:

* * *

**External Links**

Entertainment.ie does provide links to other websites. Whilst we do check the validity of other websites and never link to any bogus websites, you should always check other website’s own Privacy Policies and Terms of Use. 

**Data Protection**

We update our Privacy Policy from time to time as legislation and internal operating procedures change. Please keep an eye on this page for any updates or changes. 

Contact our Data Protection Officer at [requests@packed.house](mailto:requests@packed.house) for any further clarifications or personal data requests. Whilst we aim to address any questions or queries as soon as possible, please allow up to 30 working days for a response. 

For more information on data protection, please visit [www.dataprotection.ie](https://www.dataprotection.ie/) & <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en>
